<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Master Stroke</title>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>This is where I show off to the world</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 22:58:47 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 22:58:47 +0530</lastBuildDate>

    
      <item>
        <title>Day 3</title>
        <link>/blog/2014/11/21/Day-3</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <author>Dave</author>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got to say, today was one awesome day. I woke up early and was fully energised to make it a very productive one. Went for a jog. And to my surprise, I treaded more mileage than I expected. After a few rounds in the institute stadium, I walked/jogged till the main gate, which is atleast two kilometers away and came back. Got really tired there for a minute, but I could feel the energy come back after a good bath and breakfast. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To my surprise again, I studied a bit. A bit is a lot these days. If I do a sensus, the amount of time I have spent on coursework is negligibly low this semester. Gathered up the courage to go meet my project guide today. He was out of station. I need to get past this elephant in the room with him. Need to confess that I didn&amp;#39;t do enough work and get an extension. After visiting him, mounted on my borrowed cycle to get back to hostel.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aha, that&amp;#39;s when I thought, why not bike a bit and add a few burn in my Noom Coach (By the way, that app is really good to keep track of your weight loss). Cycled quite fast till main gate again and back. I should explore more!
&lt;br /&gt;
Academically, nothing much happened after that. Watched this serial &amp;quot;Madam Secretary&amp;quot; and wasted a lot of time. But, amazingly, didn&amp;#39;t feel so bad about it today. This better lifestyle, even for a day, seems to be good for my morale. 
&lt;br /&gt;
Played a bit of football after a long time (more like, never). I could feel my heart plunging in and out very hard. I should do this more often.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh..almost forgot. Noom Coach says my calorie intake for today is 2969. That&amp;#39;s really on the high end. I shouldn&amp;#39;t have taken that glucose gulps after the football game. Burned 1200 today. That&amp;#39;s could be a record for me. Need to do more and more. Feeling excited!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Signing off on a good day!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 2</title>
        <link>/blog/2014/11/20/Day-2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <author>Dave</author>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I started this day horribly. Although I had a presentation to get to at 10 o&amp;#39;clock, I woke up rather late. After hastily winding up the codes and plotting some stupid graph, reached my professor&amp;#39;s office 15 minutes late. After a quick scolding, disappointed sighs from the professor, got out of the place. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
I was supposed to work out in the morning to add up to this challenge. Well, that didn&#39;t happen. Worse still, I ate some vadai in the morning which did not suit well to my stomach. I slept of at an odd hour without having any food at all. By evening, had a terrible headache and couldn&#39;t even think properly.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Vomited profusely after a disturbing sleep. It was then that I decided to get out of my room. Walking slowly through the peaceful and beautiful campus, I could feel a lot of my stress and hence the headache slowly diffuse away. Passed by the Siva temple on the way. I think I should go there when it&#39;s aloof. The place feels so calming in its natural silence.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
After the walk, ate an Aloo Paratha from mess. Not the best food for someone who should be on diet. But, I had to eat something. Came back and slept early. Headache was back by then. Gulped about three fifth of a Crocin pill and slept off. I could feel the pill working. Body heated up and down overnight and can&#39;t help but say I slept deep. Although, I plan not to take any more medicine for these silly stuff.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;| Item          | Quantity      | Calories  |
| ------------- |:-------------:| ---------:|
| Vadai         | 4             |   276     |
| Aloo Paratha  | 1             |   211     |
| Curd          | 1 cup         |   138     |
|-------------------------------------------|
|   ||                              625 |&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
625 is a really good cut back. But, I need to go more and more intensive.Without of course breaking myself.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
See you tomorrow!
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Day 1</title>
        <link>/blog/2014/11/19/Day-1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <author>Dave</author>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I woke up and decided that enough is enough. I have had too many of those days swelled up in frustration and desperation. I need to transform in to a nonchalant and better being and find my purpose in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt; It&amp;#39;s not easy. I know. It won&amp;#39;t be a short journey. I know. 
&lt;br /&gt; But I need to figure out the ways of life. Run experiments, solve life&amp;#39;s mysteries and strive for the best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt; Target 1 : A better-looking me &lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon constant self reflections and though processes, I realise that my major drawback is lack of self-love. People say &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Oh, dear, how you look is not important. What&amp;#39;s underneath is what matters!&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe they are right. But in this superficial rat-race world, I realise that I need to strive to look best for my survival.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A more healthier and acceptable physique is what I am going to achieve. I know that it&amp;#39;s going to be tough. Lot of the daily posts that I plan to post here are going to be about me achieving that target.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deadline : April 30 - 2015.
Reminders have been set
Timers are about to begin from this date.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the best to myself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    

  </channel>
</rss>
